[Music]
the following is a production of Frankie
Freitas and the internet resume of
holography
[Music]
hello everyone this is Frankie Francis
and welcome to another week of holotalk
for the week of May 10 1998 we're live
on the world wide web with the webcam so
if you're tuned in right now hello how
are you and thank you for tuning in
I'm going to be working on the webcam
this week we're going to make a few
changes and I was wondering how long I
would have this connectex quick cam
before I would rip it apart so I'm going
to take it apart I have some Optics I
want to add to it which will give you a
broader view of the studio
and I'm also going to start sending a
larger picture
what I'm going to do is give you the
option
starting this week that when you click
on the webcam page you'll be able to
open up the whole talk webcam show
in a separate window
so that you can take that window and
take it down to the bottom corner of
your screen and then go back to your
main browser
and continue on the world wide web
because I know a lot of you have to sit
there a new picture goes up every 60
seconds but it's it's kind of boring
just to sit there and wait for the next
picture to come up so now you can go
back to whatever surfing you happen to
enjoy doing and the picture will still
refresh it and refresh itself every 60
Seconds
but it will do so
in a separate window on the bottom of
your screen
we're going to be showing you a bare
laser tube tonight as promised to helium
neon laser tube now I know a lot of you
already know what a laser laser tube
looks like when it's lit up but keep in
mind there are a lot of listeners who
are students and teachers amateurs and
hobbyists who have a small five
milliwatt tubes that are in the
cylindrical housings and they do not
ever get a chance to see what's going on
inside the housing when that tube has
went up so what I'm going to do this
week is light up one of the tubes for
you in just a little bit and bring the
webcam over and show you exactly what a
helium neon laser tube looks like when
it's lit up last week we did a laser
diode and that was pretty cool too
next week May 14th on the webcam
Thursday night 11 o'clock
I have an interesting
project that I'm working on making
hologram I received a package from a
gentleman named Jerry Robinson Jerry is
an independent researcher into the John
F Kennedy assassination and he's he has
a body of work which he sent to me it's
called denial
continue cover-up by the government with
the help of the establishment press of
the truth about the assassination of
President Kennedy and here I'll hold the
book up to the camera you can see the
book that he's published
along with the book he sent me a couple
of bullets and these bullets are the
same type of bullet that was used in the
gun of Lee Harvey Oswald who allegedly
acted
shooting president
the two boats are quite different one
bullet looks as if it has not been ever
shot from a gun in the first place
and this is supposedly the way the Magic
Bullet works worked in the single bullet
theory
and that theory goes that there was one
bullet that was shot from the rifle of
Lee Harvey Oswald that entered the rear
of President Kennedy's neck and exited
the front of his
it then proceeded to go into the back of
John Connolly who was governor who was
sitting in front of John F Kennedy
traveling through his chest and
puncturing one of his lungs
including the front of his chest
continuing on to go through his wrist
and shatter the bones in the wrist and
eventually winding up embedded in his
thigh
now at the hospital Parkland Memorial
Hospital where Governor Conley and
President Kennedy were taken after the
shooting
this bullet supposedly worked with John
Connolly's thigh and was found on the
stretcher next to him
and if you've ever seen any of the
pictures from the one Commission report
you've seen that this bullet looks as if
it had never been shot from a gun in the
first place
now that would be all well and good but
the second thought in this package is a
bullet that was taken
and shot from the same type of rifle
that Lee Harvey Oswald used
using the same bullet
same type of bullet and it was shot into
the wrist of a cadaver
this bullet is so distorted and so
smashed up
that it's almost impossible to believe
that I bet other bullet did so much
damage and still managed
to look the way that it looked after it
did all the damage so next week if you
log on May 14th Thursday night 11
o'clock on the webcam page I'm going to
show you these bullets
show you the one that represents the
pristine bullet and I'll show you the
bullet that was shot into the roofs of
the cadaver
and you decide for yourself
okay
internet resources
I'm currently working on a new site
which is going to be a part of the web
VM site but it's actually going to be a
separate site unto itself and it's going
to be for Internet Resources
so if you're interested in lasers and
Holograms and holography and Optics
I'm hoping that this is going to be a
valuable resource for you
now you know I already have a link page
and it's a fairly comprehensive
comprehensive listing of links on the
world wide web that pertain to lasers
and Holograms
this resource site is going to be a
little different it's going to be an
interactive resource site
and what it's going to allow you to do
it's going to allow you to search for
information but it does a little bit
more than just a search engine it's
going to be broken up into a number of
different parts the first part is going
to be a worldwide web search
and it will be a pull down window with
up to 50 keywords that will be
cross-referenced with holography
and you can choose what keywords you
want to search with under either lasers
or Holograms
and we'll go out and it will query all
of the top search engines and then
compile those results
into one listing that it will send back
to you
a second part of the site will go out
and check for Usenet or News Group
listings
two parts one within the past 60 days
and the other part will be Archives of
Usenet postings going all the way back
anything to do with lasers and Holograms
a third section
will work just about the same way as the
other two except for the fact that it
will query up to 100 newspapers
and we'll find all the relative articles
from lasers and Holograms
cross-reference with the keywords that
you select
pile that information and send you the
results back right on the page
the final part will be a books and print
where you can go out and find out what
books are currently published
that can help you learn about the things
that you need to learn about concerning
lasers and Holograms I'm hoping to have
this finished
shortly
but I will have it finished by June 1st
so I'll keep you up to date on that
I hope it turns out to be a valuable
resource for you when you're doing
research for lasers and holograms on the
world wide web Dr John Perry who is
scheduled to be a guest this week are
two schedules were so mixed up this week
that I cannot interview him until Monday
at 4 30.
now considering Monday
is the day that this show is the hardest
hit or the most listened to day of the
week
I certainly don't want to record his
conversation Monday at 4 30 and then put
it up Monday night
so what I'm going to do is we're just
going to skip it this week
and if you come back on May 17th
that will be the week for John Perry
I think that's probably the best way to
handle it we can't always get the
schedules together but we're always on
the air we always get to show up one way
or the other John Perry's going to be up
May 17th instead of this week
if you're interested in knowing what are
or who our upcoming guests are going to
be there's a link on the left hand side
of the page that says updates and guests
I believe it says that just click on
that and it'll tell you how you can get
on the email list that
yes I know we're booked into the well
into the fall of 98. we've got a lot of
exciting guests and topics coming up
and the email list will let you know a
number of different things
as I book guests
which means they they will be booked in
the fall if they arrange to come on show
now I will let you know now as their
books for instance this week I just
booked Melissa Crenshaw for late fall
so you would know that Melissa Crenshaw
will be coming up in the fall if you
were on the email list
we will also let you know what the topic
of that week was because the email list
goes out to you on Fridays
and by then we've already got the
interviews finished and I can give you a
little bit of background information on
what's coming up on Sunday and what you
can expect to listen to with the guests
that we have so that you already know
before you even log on to listen to the
site and so on and so forth It's a
valuable resource so check it out and if
you'd like to get on the email list it
tells you how to do it because I'm a
workshop programs
my summer workshop programs are just
about getting ready to start up here in
Allentown Pennsylvania this is the 15th
year folks that I've had the summer
workshop programs here evening workshops
during the week
afternoon and evening workshops on the
weekends you can come in and bring an
object of your choice from home
and make your own one-of-a-kind hologram
right here in the lab and take it home
with you at the end of the workshop
very popular program so I'm going to
have some information on the worldwide
web about that shortly and you may want
to come in and take one of the workshops
lasers and Holograms coming to the
Discovery Center of Science and
Technology June 6 through September 13th
from the Pacific Science Center
if you live in Boston New York
Philadelphia Baltimore Washington D.C
Carter it's a very easy Drive folks you
can probably get right on the highway
and more than likely drive without even
a stoplight before you get to the
Discovery Center I think the first
stoplight you would hit from any of
those cities once you're in the highway
would be about three blocks from the
center so it's a straight Shoe Drive
it's going to be a very interesting show
okay so that's going to wrap it up for
this week we're going to keep it as a
short show John Perry next week he's
from holographics North By the way they
produce very large format Holograms and
if you're the type of holographer that
works with two and a half or four by
five plates or maybe even eight by tens
you may find it very interesting to find
out exactly what goes into making these
large Holograms that are meters square
I'm curious as to how they process them
what do they use swimming pools like how
would you process a hologram that's
meters squared so we'll find out all
that information from Dr Perry I'll be
interviewing him Monday at 4 30 and his
show will go up on me May 17th so tune
in
to get this Thursday night
11 o'clock Eastern time tune in to the
webcam
live webcam and see these John F Kennedy
assassination test bone
I think you'll find it pretty
interesting so this is Frankie face for
hollow talk thank you for tuning in and
I'll see you next week
foreign